number three asks which of the following
functional groups does not contain a
carbonal so again what is a carbonal a
carbonal is cble Bond o and then there's
stuff on either side and different
functional groups will contain a
carbonal depending on what that stuff on
either side is we will call them
different functional groups so what is
an alahh an alahh is C double bond o
where we have alkal on one side and a
hydrogen on the the other side so the
thing that makes it an alahh is that one
side of the carbonal has hydrogen it is
basically the end of a carbon chain what
about a carboxilic acid a carboxilic
acid is cbond O and then o so instead of
just an H we have o there and the
presence of that other oxygen atom is
what makes this a carboxilic acid then
we have ether so an ether is an oxygen
atom with alkal on either side